reolink.com 2019-08-24

# Privacy Policy – Reolink

Last updated on June 6, 2019.

Your privacy is important to Reolink. We've developed this Privacy Policy that covers what information we collect, how we collect it, how we use it and what choices you have about it.

Some of the concepts might seem a little technical, and we've tried our best to explain them in a simple and clear way. Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with our privacy practices and let us know if you have any questions.

This Privacy Policy governs your use of Reolink official website https://reolink.com/, including Reolink subdomain sites around the world (collectively, "Site"), and it also applies to the security products we sell, the official software we offer (Reolink App and Client specifically), as well as all other services Reolink provides, including, but not limited to Reolink Cloud and technical support (collectively, "Products and Services").

BY USING REOLINK SECURITY PRODUCTS AND SERVICES, YOU CONSENT TO THE DATA PRACTICES PRESCRIBED IN THIS STATEMENT.

* ## What Information We Collect

We collect the following information when you visit our Site or using our Products and Services:

### 1\. Personal Information

1). **Contact information.** When you register a Reolink account, contact us via email, or register Reolink products you bought, we might collect that information such as your name, email address and phone number.

2). **Payment information.** We might collect information necessary to complete your purchase such as credit card number and mailing address, and any other information you choose to provide to us when making a purchase.

3). **Information you share or post on our website.** We might collect information that you post in a public space on our website, such as the Community (we also call it Forum).

4). **Social media information.** If you access our websites using your Facebook/Google account login, we may receive personal information about you such as your name, email address, and gender. Any personal information that we collect from your Facebook/Google account may depend on your Facebook/Google account's privacy settings.

5). **Third party personal information.** If you choose to provide us with a third party's personal information (such as name, email, and phone number), you must ensure that you have the third party's permission to do so. Examples include providing us with the names and images that you associate with account users or forwarding reference or marketing material to a friend.

### 2\. Device Information

1). **Device setup information.** We collect information related to the setup and usage of Reolink products, such as device name, model, UID, and adjustments you make to the product setup.

2). **Technical information about the device** such as firmware and software version, WiFi signal strength and environmental data from Reolink’s sensors like ambient light in the room.

3). **Video and audio.** Reolink Products enables you to determine the purpose and the means for which you collect video and audio signals data. When you enable the recording or streaming features of your camera, we may record and process video and/or audio recordings from the device, subject to your instruction, configuration and settings. This may include capturing and emailing to you portions of this data as part of a notification or analyzing the data to identify motion or other events. If you subscribe to Reolink Cloud, we will capture, process and retain video and audio data from your device for the duration of your recording subscription period (for example, 7, 30 or 60 days) and you will be able to access those recordings using the Services during that time.

4). **Information about your mobile device,** such as mobile device ID, device model and operating system, to enable Reolink App/Client to function properly.

5). **Information from interaction with Third Parties.** If Reolink offers any product or account connections or integrations with third-party products, applications, functionality, or services (collectively, "Third-Party Products and Services"), and you choose to enable or connect to such Third-Party Products and Services through the means authorized and directed by Reolink and/or such third-party partners, you acknowledge and agree that we may share certain information about your Reolink Product with such third parties for account authentication and management, and to enable the activation, connection and integration with and to such Third-Party Products and Services on such third parties’ platforms. For example, some of our Products use third-party voice assistance services like Google Assistant, which collects information including your Product name to display it on Google-enabled devices.

In some cases, Reolink or the Third-Party partner will instead (or also) ask for permission to control the Reolink products and services and/or third-party products and Services that you have activated and connected to. Your consent is required to allow any of these exchanges or requests for control and you will be able to revoke or disable it at any time.

We may also receive information such as connected monitor model from Google and other third-party partners and combine that with the information in your Reolink account to determine eligibility and efficacy of our programs.

Any Reolink data that you choose to share with a third party, either directly or by or on behalf of Reolink through the authorizations, integrations and connections, is governed by that third party’s privacy policy while in that party’s possession.

Any data that Reolink receives from third parties will be processed and stored by Reolink and will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This information may be processed in the same ways as any other data.

* ## How We Use Your Information

We will not sell, share, or rent your personal information to any third party or use your e-mail address for unsolicited mail.

1). We use information to respond to your requests or questions. For example, if you ask for a user manual, we will send it to you. We might use your information to confirm your subscription. We will also give you technical support if you are eligible for it. When we provide support, we may use the information you provided or information we've gathered passively.

2). We use information to communicate with you about our relationship. We may contact you about your account or subscription. We may contact you about this Policy or our website Terms.

3). We use information to improve our website or our products and services. For example, we might conduct surveys so we know our customers. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary. If you participate, we will request certain personal information from you and we may use the information you provide to improve our products and services, and to administer those programs.

4). We use information for marketing purposes. For example, we might send you special promotions or offers. We might also tell you about new features or products. These would be our own offers or products. We may track your activities and show you ads we think you might like.

5). We use information for security purposes. We may use information to protect our company, our customers, or our websites.

6). We use information to talk to parents or guardians to get permission. We may use contact information to get permission from parents for children who want to use our site.

7). We use information to complete the delivery process. We render your name, address, phone number and other information necessary to the shipment companies that deliver products to you.

8). We use information as otherwise permitted by law.

* ## Your Choices and Rights About Your Information

If you have a Reolink account, you may update, correct, or delete your account information at any time by visiting your account profile page.

Likewise, if you close your Reolink account, you will not be able to sign in to Reolink Products or Services or access any of your information. However, you can open a new account at any time. Please note that while any changes you make will be reflected in active user databases within a reasonable period of time, we may retain all information you submit, as authorized under applicable law, for backups, archiving, prevention of fraud and abuse, analytics, satisfaction of legal obligations, or where we otherwise reasonably believe that we have a legitimate reason to do so. In addition, if certain information has already been provided to third parties as described in this Privacy Policy, retention of that information will be subject to those third parties' policies.

You can opt out of receiving any emails from us. To stop receiving our emails, click "Unsubscribe" in any email you get from us. Don't worry! Even if you opt-out of getting emails, we will still be sure to contact you for important updates or notices. For example, we may still contact you about your orders, you will also continue to receive critical technical information about your Reolink products.

We do not share information with third parties for their independent marketing or promotional purposes.

You can choose not to install our applications (Reolink App or Client) or not to fill out warranty. This choice may limit your warranty service.

For other personal information, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access and support so you can request that we correct the data if it is inaccurate, or delete the data if Reolink is not required to retain it by law or for legitimate business purposes.

**Your Other Options**

You have options in relation to the information that we have about you described below. To exercise these options, please contact us. If you're an EEA user, you can:

1). Access the information we hold about you.

2). Have your information corrected or deleted.

3). Object to us processing your information. You can ask us to stop using your information, including when we use your information to send you marketing emails or push notifications. If you opt out of receiving marketing messages from us, we may still send you newsletters and updates about your account or products.

4). Have the information you provided to us sent to another organization, where we hold this information with your consent or for the performance of a contract with you, where it's technically feasible.

* ## How We Use Cookies and Other Technologies

We analyze log file information and other data collected through cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technology, to collect related data when you visit our Site or use our Products and Services, including information about your browser and what sites you visit. We might also look at how and how often you use one of our applications and certain features. These technologies help us better understand user behavior, tell us which parts of our service people have used, and facilitate and measure the effectiveness of advertisements.

In some of our email messages, we use a "click-through URL" linked to content on the Site. We track this click-through data to help us measure the effectiveness of our customer communications.

* ## Third Party Analytics Service

We use third-party analytics tool -- Google Analytics to assist us with analyzing and improving our service. Google provides some additional privacy options to protect business's data. [Click here](https://privacy.google.com/businesses/) to learn more. We've read and accept updated terms and contractual protections Google made to analytics tool we've used.

To prevent Google Analytics from using your information for analytics, you may install the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on by [clicking here](https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/google-analytics-opt-out/fllaojicojecljbmefodhfapmkghcbnh?hl=en).

* ## Data Security

Reolink takes precautions, including administrative, technical, and physical measures, to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

The online services offered by Reolink use encryption on web pages where personal information is collected (for example, credit card and other payment information). To use these services, we recommend you use an SSL-enabled browser such as Internet Explorer, Firefox, Chrome, or Safari. Doing so protects the confidentiality of your personal information while it's transmitted over the Internet.

Please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot and do not guarantee that information about you will not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

* ## Data Transferring

Reolink sells products and offers services to Northern America, Oceania, Europe, and Asia. (Check Where We Ship.) By using our websites and solutions or providing any Personal Information, you agree to the transfers, processing, and storage of your Personal Information outside of your country of residence. When we transfer your Personal Information to other countries, we will protect that information as described in this Privacy Policy or as disclosed to you at the time of data collection.

When personal data is transferred from the European Economic Area (EEA), we take special safeguards to ensure that the protection travels with the data, including having standard clauses approved by the European Commission in our contracts with parties that receive information outside the EEA.

The privacy protections and the rights of authorities to access your information in these countries may not be the same as in your home country. And we may not provide the same level of protection as those in your country.

* ## Data Retention

Reolink makes it easy for you to keep your personal information accurate, complete, and up to date. We will retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

* ## Reolink Cloud

### 1\. Data collection and data access

Reolink Cloud collects the information you provide, including your account information (your profile, email address, username, etc.), device information (device name, model, type, etc.) and information about video footage you uploaded to Reolink Cloud (video length, video title, and video format, etc.).

Reolink Cloud will access this information when you agree to enable Cloud storage service, subscribe to a plan, and bind your device. We take your account security very seriously. We will not sell, share, or rent the collected information to any third party or use it for any illegal activities.

### 2\. Data in transit

To protect data in transit between Reolink Cloud on Reolink official website or Reolink Mobile App and our servers, Reolink uses HTTP/1.1 over TLSv1.2, the strongest data communication protocol by now, recommended by the Payment Card Industry Security Standards Council. For maximum data protection, your data are encrypted by 2048-bit RSA and 128-bit AES-GCM algorithms, ensuring the confidentiality, integrity and authenticity of your data during transmission.

### 3\. Data storage

Data storage is powered by Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3). Videos uploaded to Reolink Cloud are stored in highly secure AWS data centers with the disaster recovery backups. These videos are protected by our Access Key and cannot be accessed by anyone without your permission.

* ## California Do Not Track Notice

Reolink does not currently respond or take any action with respect to web browser "do not track" signals or other mechanisms that provide consumers the ability to exercise choice regarding the collection of personally identifiable information about a user's online activities over time and across third-party web sites or online services.

* ## Children's Privacy

The service is not intended for or directed to persons under the age of 18. We require that use of the service and all purchases made through it be by individuals who are 18 years of age or older. Reolink does not permit registration by and will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under 18. If Reolink learns that we have collected the personal information of a child under 18 we will take steps to delete the information as soon as possible.

* ## Links to Other Sites or Have Third Party Services on Our Site

We may link to other sites or have third party services on our site that we don't control. If you click on a link to a third party site, you will be taken to websites we do not control. This policy does not apply to the privacy practices of that website. Read the privacy policy of other websites carefully. We are not responsible for these third party sites.

* ## Changes and Updates on This Policy

Please revisit this page periodically to stay aware of any changes to this Policy, which we may update from time to time. Your continued use of Reolink Products and Services after the revised Policy has become effective indicates that you have read, understood and agreed to the current version of this Policy.

For any questions or suggestions about this Privacy Policy and your personal information, you can reach us by using the information on our Contact Us page, or by email at dpo@reolink.com.
